West Hartford, CT. Elmwood Community Church records, 1867-2024. RG5531
Congregational Library & Archives
- Church boards, 1921-2024
  - Deacons, 1936-2022
    - Board for Lay Life Schedule Pamphlets, 1975-1989 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Board for Lay Life Miscellaneous, 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 1992-1998 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 2000-2007 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 2009-2012 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 2013-2020 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Deacons' Minutes, 2021-2022 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Board for Lay Life Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Elmweds, 1948-1967
    This subseries contains minutes and associated documents from the Elmweds groups which was an organization for married couples at Elmwood.
    - Elmweds Minutes, 1948-1953 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Elmweds Minutes, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Elmweds Minutes, 1961-1967 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Men's club, 1955-1982
    This subseries contains minutes from the men's club at Elmwood.
    - Men's Club Minutes, 1955-1963 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Men's Club Minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Trustees, 1927-2024
    This subseries contains records including minutes, reports, correspondence, and other related documents from the board of trustees which was at times known as the board of stewardship.
    - Trustees' Minutes, 1927-1935 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Trustees' Miscellaneous, 1928-1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Board of Stewardship Minutes, 1977-1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Board of Stewardship Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Board of Stewardship Minutes, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 1993-1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 2005-2009 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 2010-2014 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 2015-2019 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Trustees' Minutes, 2020-2023 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Junior Christian Endeavor Minutes, 1931-1938 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Tambo Club Minutes, 1946-1951 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Executive Committee, Trustees, and Finance Committee Minutes, 1952-1955 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Executive Committee, Trustees, and Finance Committee Minutes, 1955-1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Finance Committee and Trustees Minutes, 1957-1964 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Executive Committee, Trustees, and Finance Committee Minutes, 1958-1961 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Executive Committee, Trustees, and Finance Committee Minutes, 1961-1966 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Executive Committee, Trustees, and Finance Committee Minutes, 1966-1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Board for Christian Outreach Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Board and Committee Minutes, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Board Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Council and Board Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Board Minutes, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Council and Board Minutes, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Photostat Copy of Minutes, 1921-1952 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Administrative records, 1875-2023
  This series contains records relating to the administration of Elmwood Community Church including annual reports, financial reports, correspondence, legal records, building plans, employment documents, committee records, renovation and property records, attendance books, minutes, memorial fund donations and records, constitutions, and other related documents.
  - Annual reports, 1921-2023
    This subseries contains annual reports for the church.
    - Annual Reports, 1921-1922 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1922-1923 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports, 1930-1933 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Original Annual Reports, 1942-1946 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Original Annual Reports, 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Annual Reports, 1946-1949 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Annual Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Annual Reports, 1955-1959 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Annual Reports, 1960-1964 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Annual Reports, 1965-1968 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Annual Reports, 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Annual Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Annual Reports, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1994 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Annual Reports, 1995-1999 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Annual Reports, 2000-2005 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Annual Reports, 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Annual Reports, 2009-2012 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 2013-2016 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 2017-2019 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 2020-2021 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 2022-2023 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Original Annual Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Annual Reports, 1948-1996 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Committees, 1949-2010
    This subseries contains minutes, reports, and other related documents from the various committees at the church.
    - Nominating Committee Reports, 1933-2003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Renovation Committee, 1954-2013 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Finance Committee Minutes, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Endowment Fund Minutes and Reports, 1975-2005 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Rose Committee Minutes, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Pastoral Search Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Search Committee Minutes, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Visitation Committee, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Endowment Fund Committee Minutes, 1986-1999 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Search Committee Minutes, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Operations Review Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Pastoral Search Committee, 1992-2009 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Nominating Committee Reports, 1994-2007 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Endowment Fund Donation Letters, 1995-1998 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - New Organist Committee Minutes, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Pastoral Relations Committee, 1997-2006 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Music Committee, 1998-2004 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Accessibility Committee Minutes, 2000-2007 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Endowment Fund Committee Minutes, 2002-2006 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Endowment Fund Committee, 2004-2007 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Accessibility Committee Minutes, 2007-2010 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Memorial funds, 1940-2022
    This subseries contains donation letters, minutes, and reports relating to the memorial funds.
    - Memorial Funds Gifts, 1940-1972 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Memorial Fund Account Book, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Memorial Gifts, 1958-1980 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Memorial Funds Account Book, 1972-1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Hymnal Memorial Donations, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 1984-1989 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Memorial Gifts, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Memorial Gift Ledger, 1990-2003 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Memorial Fund Committee, 1991-2021 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Memorial Committee Reports, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Memorial Donation Ledger, 2004-2022 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2010 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2011 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2012 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2013 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2014-2015 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2016-2017 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2017-2018 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2018 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2019-2020 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2020 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Memorial Donation Letters, 2021-2022 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Carllion Bell Fund Memorials and Contributions, 1961 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Building Plans, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Physical Access
    This item can not be unfolded due to fragility.
  - Payment Letters, 1875-1878 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1876-1881 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Social Union Minutes, 1877-1878 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Financial Plegde Lists, 1897-1900 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Copy of Chapel Association Minutes, 1899-1921 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Financial Subscriptions, 1901-1902 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Pastor Correspondence, 1902-1912 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Chapel Association Contributions and Correspondence, 1908-1910 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1910-2013 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Chapel Association Minutes and Account Book, 1915-1927 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Reports, and Programs, 1920-1925 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence and Minutes, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Account Book, 1921-1923 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Early Church Records, 1921-1945 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, 1922-1930 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Building Fund Campaign, 1922-1935 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Year Book Reports, 1922-1959 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Annual Reports and Correspondence, 1923-1925 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Land Parcel Records, 1923-1929 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Canvass Lists and Instructions, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence and Reports, 1925 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Financial Reports and Receipts, 1925-1934 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Ct Missionary Society Aid Application, 1925-1953 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Annual Reports and Correspondence, 1926 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Building Fund Financial Reports, 1927-1928 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Building Society Grant Information, 1930-1931 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1930-1932 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Stewardship, 1934-1969 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Church Bonds and Completion Fund, 1935-1944 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Julia Green Loan, 1940-1951 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Parsonage and Church Loans, 1943-1952 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Attendance Book, 1944-1958 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - West Hartford Manufacturer's Bonds, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence and Announcements, 1945-2019 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Building Expansion, 1947-1949 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Expansion Fund Canvass, 1947-1957 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Church Alterations Agreement and Specifications, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Heating System Renovation, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Expansion Fund Canvass, 1957-1958 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Attendance Book, 1957-1959 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Cambridge St. Lease, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Folding Doors, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Budgets, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Maintenance and Insurance, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Attendance Book, 1959-1961 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Bell Fund Account Book, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Attendance Book, 1962-1965 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Staffing Evaluations and Meeting Minutes, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - Associate Pastor Position, 1965-1969 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Staff Responsibilities and Agreements, 1968-1993 (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Canvass Plan and Instructions, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - Attendance Book, 1969-1973 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Confirmation Class, 1972-1978 (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Year Book Reports, 1973-1990 (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - Dorothy Tucker Estate, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Canvass List, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Special Meeting Minutes, 1982-2009 (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Road Easement, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - Attendance Book, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence and Church Future, 1990-2016 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Pastor Agreements, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Robert Sheehan Estate, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - Attendance Book, 1992-1995 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - Stewardship Committee Pledges, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - Memorial Garden, 1997-2004 (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Church Profile, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Memorial Garden Committee and Gifts, 1999-2004 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence, 2003-2023 (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Stewardship Campaigns, 2004-2008 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Confirmation Class Correspondence, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Stewardship Campaigns, 2008-2015 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Safe Church Policy, 2013-2015 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Lawrence Eddins Will, 2015 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Stewardship Campaigns, 2015-2023 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Chapel Records Highlights, 1907-1921 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Chapel Association Subscription Ledger, 1909-1921 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Building Specifications, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Renovation and Maintenance, 1929-1960 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Constitutions and By-laws, 1931-2007 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Mortgages, 1932-1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Church Funds Account Book, 1937-1951 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Correspondence, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Canvass and Contribution Lists, 1945-1950 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Treasurer's Reports, 1948-1950 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Renovations, 1957-1958 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Barnum Trust, 1976-2004 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Sarah Sears Estate, 1978-1992 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Claire Shipman Will, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Thelma Behler Estate, 2004-2008 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Disbursements, 1943-1951 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Receipts, 1943-1951 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Floor Plans, undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - General Fund Account Ledger, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Building Plans, 1948-2008 (Folder 1)
  - Site Plans and Charter Members, 1921-2021 (Folder 2)
  - Building and Site Plans, 1947-1989 (Folder 3)
  - Building Drawing, undated (Item 6)
- Church history, 1875-2024
  This series contains records relating to the history of Elmwood Community Church which was formerly the Elmwood Union Chapel Association. The records include programs, historical highlights, historian records, newspaper articles, member profiles, newsletters, pamphlets, sermons, announcements, and documents relating to various events.
  - Member profiles, 1921-2021
    This subseries contains records including newspaper articles, programs, correspondence, and other documents relating to various members and pastors of the church.
    - Board Member Profiles, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - James English, 1921-1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Charles Tracy, 1925-2008 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Sterling White, 1945-1962 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Milton Barlow, 1953-2009 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Thomas McVey, 1959-2008 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Carl Christensen, 1963-2012 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Clergy, 1963-2021 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Robert Loggie, 1965-1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - William Jeffrey Jr., 1970-2009 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Philip Conte, 1973-1988 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Charter Member Profiles, 1982-1984 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Richard Grobe, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Rachel Durkin, 1991-2010 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - John Buttrick, 1992-1997 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Susan Lyon, 1996-2003 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Nick Davis, 1998-2007 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Ruth Porter, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Bob Woodward, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Mason Ellison, 2009-2018 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - David Congdon, 2010-2013 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Barbara Hesse, 2013-2018 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Julia Faxon, 1871-1954 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Charles Tracy Newstories, 1926-1961 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Newsletters, 1921-2023
    This subseries contains newsletters from the church with the weekly bulletin in earlier years and the "Elmwords" in later years.
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1921-1922 (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1923 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1924-1933 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Bulletin, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - "Elmwords", 1980-1984 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - "Elmwords", 1985-1989 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - "Elmwords", 1990-1999 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - "Elmwords", 2000-2005 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - "Elmwords", 2006-2011 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - "Elmwords", 2012-2019 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - "Elmwords", 2020-2023 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - "Elmwords", 1965-1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - "Elmwords", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Publicity, 1897-1916 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Children's Stories, 1903 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Church History, 1906-2013 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Calendar, 1910 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Tri-fold Board Materials, 1911-1984 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Ordination Services, 1915-2003 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Calendar Pamphlet, 1916 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Building a Church, 1920-1949 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Cornerstone Laying, 1927 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Show Programs, 1931-1955 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Events and Announcements, 1933-2016 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - 25th Anniversary, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Historian's Reports, 1947-1964 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Pamphlets and Brochures, 1952-2010 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Service Programs, 1957-2017 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - 40th Anniversary, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Holiday Fair, 1962-2013 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Sermons, 1964-1970 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Mortgage Burning, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - 50th Anniversary, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - 60th Anniversary, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Richard Grobe Sermons, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - 65th Anniversary, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Historian's Articles, Correspondence, and Notes, 1986-2018 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - 50/40 Celebration, 1987-2021 (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Historian's Report, 1989-2006 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Historical Highlights, 1991-2006 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - 75th Anniversary, 1996 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - 80th Anniversary, 2001 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Korean Partnership, 2002-2007 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Thanksgiving Interfaith Service, 2004-2006 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - New Member Reception, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Youth Trips, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Buiding Community Retreat, 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Veteran's Day Recognition, 2005-2017 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - 85th Anniversary, 2006 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Blessing of the Animals, 2006-2017 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Easter Flower Lists, 2006-2022 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Church Break In, 2012 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - 140th Anniversary Cookbook, 2013 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Alice Cook Donation, 2017 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Church Legacy Letters, 2020-2024 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Church Drawings, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Historical Documents used for 140th Anniversary, 1875-1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1913-2013 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Publicity, 1921-2015 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Service Programs, 1939-1947 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Auction, 1947-1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Memorial Day Program, 1949-1961 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Service Programs, 1950 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Save the Children Foundation Sponsorships, 1953-2006 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Publicity, 1956-1962 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Organ and Carllion, 1961-2014 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Christmas Flowers Lists, 2005-2021 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - 140th Anniversary, 2011-2013 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Save the Children Sponsorship Profile, 1953 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Yearly miscellaneous records, 1921-1995
  This series contains administrative and historical records intentionally organized by separate years including newspaper articles, reports, programs, correspondence, minutes, constitutions, and other documents.
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1924 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Administrative Records, 1926 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Administrative Records, 1929 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1931 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1937 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1939-1942 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Administrative Records, 1944 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Administrative Records, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1983-1989 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1921-1923 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Administrative Records, 1927 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - News Articles, 1925 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Administrative Records, 1928 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1934 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1935 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1936 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1945 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1948 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1949 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1951 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1953 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1954 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1955 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous Records, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 49)